Looks like the team behind the Kim Ketu
model has introduced a significant new
development with the launch of okay
computer an aentic AI mode designed to
go far beyond traditional chat
capabilities which is where they've
introduced the new agent mode to the
Kimik K2 model. OK computer acts as an
AI product and engineering team. It's
capable of moving from simple text
prompts to complex multi-step websites,
mobile first designs, and even editable
slide decks. It is able to process
massive data sets up to million rows and
transform them into interactive
dashboards for analysis as well as
visualization. Essentially, the new Kim
K2 computer is an agent mode that can
autonomously automate any sort of task
from building full stack applications to
browsing the web to creating images and
so much more. The system is trained to
work natively with tools like file
systems, browsers, as well as the
terminal. And it gives the ability to
execute tasks rather than just
describing them. It's built on
turbocharged version of K2 and it
supports more steps, tokens, and tools
that standard chat modes aren't capable
of doing. It allows for deeper reasoning
and more complex operations. This
upgrade overall gives the model a degree
of autonomy and it enables it to scoop
projects, create surveys, design
workflows, and rapidly build almost
anything. And what you'll realize while
using OK Computer is that it is
something that acts like a generalist AI
agent in terms of having all the
different tool sets that a general agent
would be capable of doing like deep
research, data analysis, creating files,
using the terminal, and so much more.
This is something that you can access
for free directly through the Kimi
chatbot. Just take a look at this demo
where the Kimik K2 Asian mode was able
to build a Minecraft clone which looks
absolutely amazing. You have different
terrains. You have the ability to walk,
place blocks, even break it. And it
implemented all the different physics a
part of the Minecraft game. And it was
able to easily develop this with the
Asia mode quite rapidly.
To access the new agent mode, you're
going to need to head over to Kim's
chatbot, which I'll leave a link to in
the description below. And you can
simply create an account completely for
free. And to access the okay mode or the
agent mode, just simply enable it by
clicking on this. And you can see that
there's only three free sessions per
month available, which is kind of
unfortunate. I wished that they would
give a lot more access, but I guess this
is better than nothing. But you're going
to be able to get pretty good
generations with the free usage. And you
can obviously just create multiple
accounts and just get more usage out of
that. But after enabled, you can now
work on building anything full stack
apps doing deep analysis on your data
where you can process millions of rows
through Excel sheets that you can simply
upload or just have it do deep research
and create various sorts of reports. You
have a lot of flexibility with this. I'm
just testing it out, but I simply had it
requested to build a crypto trading
deck, a crypto trading platform where
you can trade various sorts of
cryptocurrencies. And you can see that
it first starts off by creating a to-do
list, a plan that would be deployed to
multiple agents to tackle all these
different tasks like researching and
planning the deck's platform structure
as well as the feature set, designing
the interactive components for trading
interface, and a couple other things.
And from there, it's going to work on
the deep research phase where it's going
to work on compiling different sources
to help give more context for the agents
to actually work with to build our
product, which is a dex. And what I love
about this Asia mode is that it also has
ability to create images on its own. It
has ability to write code obviously,
which it's doing at this current moment.
And it's going to work on thoroughly
taking its time to build out our
application. You can see there's 12
different subtasks part of this process
of creating our app and it's currently
at the seven step and over time it's
going to work on thoroughly building out
a highquality application for us. Also,
just a quick side note, if you haven't
noticed on my second channel recently, I
have been constantly posting new AI news
content with my team. So, if you are
interested in learning on what is
happening on a daily basis in the AI
space, I highly recommend that you take
a look at this with the link in the
description below. Now, yes, this is
free, but the only downside I personally
saw is that it takes a really long time
to get your generations outputed. I have
been waiting approximately 10 minutes
currently, and it's still stuck on 7 out
of 12 for the task progress of creating
our product decks.
Now, I know it may take some time to
generate whatever you had requested with
agent mode, but the quality of Alpa is
truly insane. This is our trading deck,
which looks absolutely amazing. The UI
looks awesome. There's actual components
that have been implemented to our app,
which looks awesome. You also have it so
that there's multiple trading pairs
inside our application, which looks
absolutely amazing. There's different
placeholders with animations and you
also have the ability to connect your
wallet. Obviously, it's not going to
work because we haven't connected
anything to it. But there's multiple
pages to this. There's a portfolio tab
which showcases your overall portfolio
which showcases your different assets
that you have a part of this wallet. You
have different markets which is pretty
cool because this is something that you
can use to trade different coins like
Salana, Avalanche, Polygon, and so many
others. But you can see the quality of
output is truly amazing. And this was
something that it had actually built
within approximately 20 minutes. It took
a bit longer than expected, but it did a
great job with its output. Let's say if
there's a certain component that needs a
lot of work on, you can go back into the
chatbot and you can request okay
computer to reiterate on that component.
So that way you can basically work with
the AI to work on implementing new
changes as well as improving the basic
function of that app. But say if you
also want to export all the contents
that it has generated like the code that
it has written, you can actually export
all of the code that it has developed
for the application through the actual
chatbot itself. So this way you can
export it and then use it elsewhere. You
can download all these different files
and then you have the ability to then
iterate on it further locally. This is
another test I had ran to generate a
mobile website and the quality is truly
insane. You can see that there's
different components that has added
animations as well as different pages
and all of this was fully coded out by
the Asian mode. OK computer it even
generated all the images a part of this
app and I also have the ability to
deploy it. So you can see the styling,
the formatting is perfect for various
sorts of apps that you can generate
based off the prompt that you give it.
If you like this video and would love to
support the channel, you can consider
donating to my channel through the super
thanks option below. Or you can consider
joining our private Discord where you
can access multiple subscriptions to
different AI tools for free on a monthly
basis, plus daily AI news and exclusive
content, plus a lot more. But that's
what's click for today's video on the
new agent mode by Kimmy. This is
something that will help you rapidly
automate and build almost anything.
Something that you can easily get
started with completely for free by just
heading over to the kimmy.com website,
their chatbot. I'll leave all these
links in the description below. And if
you do run out of these different
sessions, you can easily just go ahead
and use another account, which is
something that I personally did and
something that I would actually
recommend you do. But that's basically
it, guys. I hope you enjoyed today's
video and got some sort of value. I'll
leave these links in the description
below. Subscribe to the second channel
if you haven't already. Make sure you
join the newsletter, join the private
Discord, follow me on Twitter, and
lastly, make sure you guys subscribe,
turn on notification bell, like this
video, and please take a look at our
previous videos because there's a lot of
content that you will truly benefit
from. But with that thought, guys, have
an amazing day, spread positivity, and
I'll see you guys fairly shortly. He saw
fs.